

# MERN Stack / Web Developer

# About Me

Seeking a career with a suitable job according to my 2 years of experience and Ability, which will provide me the platform for becoming a well-recognized professional. Ultimately attaining prestige and pride for the organization and myself.



+923047624721



https://github.com/Rizwan61



https://www.linkedin.com/in/syedrizwan-ali-shah-401691213/



syedrizwanalishah56@gmail.com



Lodhran, Punjab, Pakistan

### LANGUAGE

- English
- Urdu
- Punjabi

#### **EXPERTISE**

- Front-end (React Js)
- Redux toolkit (Basic level)
- Built Rest APIs
- Back-end (Express/ NodeJs)
- Mongo db
- HTML/CSS
- Tailwinds
- Bootstraps

# **EXPERIENCE**

# Ticer Lodhran (Full Stack web development course) (2021 - 2024)

A Real-world Practice Initiative(using html css and bootstrap)

A Real-world Practice Initiative(using React Js Node Express Mongo db)

CodeLab Bahawalpur Front-End-Developer (React Js)-CodeLab Bahawalpur, Pakistan 2019 - 2021

In my role as a front end developer at CodeLab Bahawalpur company. I spearheaded the development of web application using React Js, Successfully delivering diverse projects

A Real-world Practice Initiative(using html css) A Real-world Practice Initiative 2017 - 2019

full responsive Dashboard (The code is available on my GitHub account)

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Islamia University Bahawalpur**

Master Of Computer science (MSc)2014-2017

#### Islamia University Bahawalpur

Bachelor of Computer Science (B.sc)2012-2011

# **SKILLS SUMMARY**

Front-end (React Js)

94%

Back-end (Express/ NodeJs)

76%

Project Management

85%